(Penny:)Right.
(Sheldon:)Just to be clear, do I have to stop
saying "coitus" with everyone or just you?
(Sheldon:)Everyone.
(Sheldon:)Harsh terms, but all right.
-I'll just substitute "intercourse."
-Great.
SHELDON:
Or "fornication." Yeah--
(Sheldon:)But that has judgmental overtones,
so I'll hold that in reserve.
(Penny:)So how you been?
(Sheldon:)Well, my existence is a continuum...
(Sheldon:)...so I've been what I am at each point
in the implied time period.
(Penny:)You're just coitusing with me,
aren't you?
-Buzzinga.
-Mm.
(Penny:)-How's Leonard doing?
-He seems all right...
(Sheldon:)...although he does spend
a disturbing amount of time...
(Sheldon:)...looking at photographs of you
and smelling the pillow you slept on.
Although now that I think of it,
he asked me not to tell you that.
PENNY:
I'll pretend I didn't hear it.
(Sheldon:)I'd rather you pretend I didn't say it.